let quiz   =[
    {question: "What fraction of an hour is 15 minutes? ",
option:[
    "1/3",
    "1/5",
    "1/4",
    "1/8",

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "The longest cord of a circle is called _______." ,
option:[
    "Radius",
    "Area",
   "Diameter" ,
    "Circumference",


],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "How many degees are there in a circle?",
option:[
    "90 degree",
    "45 degree",
    "180 degree",
    "360 degree",

],
answer:4, 
},
{question: "How many months make a century?",
option:[
    12,
    360,
    1200,
    120,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "An octagon is a polygon with _______ Sides",
option:[
    12,
    10,
    6,
    8,

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Find the value of the missing number in the calculation. '25 X (___+65)= (25 X 18)+(25 X 65)'",
option:[
    10,
    20,
    18,
    15,

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "If Y is the side of cube, then the volume of the cube is ______.",
option:[
    "Y*Y",
    "2*Y",
    "Y*Y*Y",
    "3*Y",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "The square of 9 is equal to ____." ,
option:[
    81,
    64,
    100,
    49,


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "Find the perimeter of rectangle with 'length:18' and 'width:10'",
option:[
    56,
    180,
    560,
    28,

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "A triangle whose all sides and angles are equal is known as _____ triangle.",
option:[
    "Square",
    "Perpendicular",
    "Equilateral",
    "Right",

    
],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "What is the square root of 441?",
option:[
    11,
    21,
    31,
    12,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "What is the value of 'a' from the given equation? '3a-5=7'",
option:[
    2,
    3,
    5,
    4,

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "25% of Rs. 2500 is equal to _____.",
option:[
    625,
    125,
    100,
    1250,

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "The simple form og 12/24 is :",
option:[
    "2/3",
    "1/2",
    "1/3",    
    "2/5",

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "The value of pi is equal to _____.",
option:[
    "11/7",
    "22/7",
    "24/7",
    "7/22",

],
answer:2, 
}]